#### **CURRICULLUM VITAE**

Mary Sheetal. S D/o Eshwar Sagar # 56/57 Flat No 304 3<sup>rd</sup> Floor, 1<sup>St</sup> Cross

MP Layout Chikkasandra T Dasarahalli, Bangalore North

Mobile No: +91 99014-63691

Email:sheetal2nim123@gmail.com

### Career objective

To get a challenging role in a professionally managing growth oriented organization & to fulfill the objective entrusted to me by the Management.

## **Details of strength**

- ➤ Intelligent & Hard worker
- > Enthusiastic & motivated
- Very good at understanding others need & offer solutions
- Good team leadership qualities
- Proven track record of adapting to challenges

#### **Personal details**

Father's Name : Eshwar Sagar DOB : 03/05/1988

Marital status : Single Mother Tongue :Tamil

Languages known: Tamil, Kannada, Hindi & English

Knowledge : Basic computer with tally

#### Academic qualification

Course/qualificati	on Institute	Board / University	Year
SSLC	Good shepherd Convent	Board of Secondary Education	2003
PUC	St. Philomena' College	University of Mysore	2005

B.com	Indian Virtual University	University of Bangalore	2010

## **Details of work experience**

### **Pay Square Consultancy**

Jan 2015 to 2016	Business Developer (BD)
May 2016 to November 2017	Reimbursement Executive
December 2017 to March 2023	Statutory Compliance Executive

# **Big Byte International BPO**

Feb 2014 to Sep 2014	International Senior Officer (ISO)
Sep 2014 to Dec 2015	Assistant Quality Analyst (AQA)

# Hinduja Global Solution's Mysore

Aug 2008 to Feb 2012	Customer Relation Officer (CRO)
Feb 2012 to Aug 2012	Knowledge & Escalation Dept. (K&E)
Aug 2012 to Feb 2013	Service Recovery Desk (SRD)
Mar 2013 to Oct 2013	Quality Analyst (QA)

### **Career Summary:**

# **PAYSQUARE Consultancy Limited, Mysore**

- ➤ Generation of UAN number for all new joiners
- Creation of ESIC IP numbers for newly joined workers
- Updating, uploading and approving KYC and modify basic details
- Preparing Client wise statutory documents for verification
- Processing PF claim forms online and offline
- Issuing ESIC TIC, running letters, working letters
- ➤ Resolving ESIC & PF corrections on respective portals
- ➤ Updating Exit details on PF, ESIC & LWF portals
- > PT Return filing state wise (Karnataka, Maharashtra, Telangana & West Bengal
- > LWF Challans state wise (Karnataka, Maharashtra & Haryana

- ➤ DSC & E-sign Registrations
- > Settled 700 odd PF claims

### **Brief of Statutory Compliance Job Profile:**

Presently working as Statutory Compliance Executive from Dec 2017 to till date. Generation of PF Challans, ESIC Challans, and Professional Tax reports month on month. Also file PT returns monthly and yearly. Generation of new joiners In PF and ESIC portal, updating Exit and approvals on PF and ESIC portal. DSC and E-sign registrations, approvals of all pending status, solving queries related to claims Transfer, withdrawals, Death claims and others related to PF. Also Worked as Reimbursement Executive, I review insurance claims and ensure that clients receive accurate reimbursement for their claims. I usually work for Medical, Vehicle, telephone and Insurance fields. Working in this process requires a strong attention to detail and office processes.

Worked as a Business Development Executive from Jan 2015 to May 2015. My job profile was to interact with new clients via telephone and speak to the company's Manager or the HR person who is handling accounts or the Payroll & explain about our service, send quotations, fix appointment with my manager and generate leads.

### Job Profile at Big Byte International BPO:

Worked at Big Byte International Process as a International Senior Officer where I need to interact with clients on the given project later was selected as Assistance Quality Analyst through IJP (Internal Job Posting) Wherein I used to audit calls, give feedback on the errors done by the associates, take huddles weekly wise and also share product updates on a daily basis.

### Job Profile at Hinduja Global Solution:

Hinduja Global Solution: As this is a Domestic call center which includes both Inbound process & Outbound process for Airtel Telecom Industry & I worked for both process, were customer calls to our customer care /call center for Queries, Requests & Complaints & it is taken care by front-end officer i.e., CRO, we act as a mid-person & personal point of contact between customer & client (AIRTEL)

As a Quality Analyst (QA): Audits calls of 3 teams each of 20 members, conducting secessions & give feedback to the associates who's score is below the target of 85% & improve them to score the given target.

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true and correct to the best knowledge & belief.

Place : MysoreThanking You,Date : 05/03/2023Mary Sheetal. S